

# **NAHID SHAIKH**

# UI/UX/WEB DESIGNER

#### **ABOUT ME**

7+ Years experience as Sr. Web/UI Designer

10 Month experience as Web Trainer

Self-learner. Highly motivated and can quickly adapt to any new environment.

Versatile team player as well as independent contributor with good problem solving skills

Able to handle project work with team as a team leader.

#### **AREA OF EXPERTISE:**

Skilled in UX & UI for Mobile Applications and Websites Extensively worked on designing Responsive websites using Bootstrap/Media Queries, HTML5, CSS3, javascript, Photoshop.

Cross browser/Cross Platform testing using Browser-Stack website (Live, Web-Based Browser Testing), also on real devices,

Testing of HTML code, responsive testing using HTML validator, Firbug with YSlow, Web developer tool.

#### CONTACT

Mobile No:- +91-9960630845

Email Id:- nahid004@gmail.com

Location:- Pune (Wagholi)

#### **SOCIAL**

Skype:- nahid.s004

Linkedin:- nahid-shaikh-4b615124

Facebook:- nahid.shaikh.3532

Behance:- www.behance.net/nahid00427a9

#### **HOBBIES**

Drawing

Chess

Music

#### LANGUAGE

English

Marathi

Hindi

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Web Trainer

Feb 2019 - till date

#### Sr. Web Designer

Jan 2013 - May 2017

### Web Designer

Dec 2010 - Dec 2012

#### Web Designer

Nov 2009 - Oct 2010

### Blend Infotech, Pune

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Jquery, Bootstrap, Photoshop, Php, Angular 2-8 Training for Students and employees

### Trident Web Infoservices, Pune (Ecomsolutions Uk company projects)

UX/UI for Mobile application and Website.

Designing responsive websites using Bootstrap/Media Queries, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Jauery, Photoshop CMS websites using core PHP.

Html validation and Cross browser/Cross Platform testing

on Browser Stack

#### T Craft Technologies, Pune

Designing and developing websites using Flash + Actionscript 2.0, php(core), Html, Css,

JavaScript, Photoshop

Designing layout (UI) of .NET web application & windows based software

## AD Shresoft IT(India) Pvt. Ltd., MIDC, Satara (Australia client)

Designing Website using Html, CSS, JavaScript, Flash (Actionscript 2.0), Adobe Photoshop, Coreldraw Designing brochure and website template

#### **PROJECTS**

UX/UI for HR Web Application

UX/UI for **Gym Mobile** Application and **Music** Application

• UI / Visituals for lot of websites (www.behance.net/nahid00427a9)

#### **EDUCATION**

2017 Certified UI/UX Designer From Felix IT Systems

**2009** M.C.A Passed from ICFAI University, Satara Branch

• 2002 B.Sc.(Chemistry) Passed from Shivaji University, Kolhapur

• 1999 H.S.C. Passed from Kolhapur Board

1997 S.S.C. Passed from Kolhapur Board

#### **TECHNICAL SKILL**

Axure		Html5	
Balsamiq	_	CSS3	
Adobe Photoshop		Bootstrap	
Adobe Illustrator		Javascript	
Adobe In design		Jquery	
Adobe XD		Core php	
Sketch		Angular	